Finally, the Rat Man ran onto the bus and came out to open his backpack. The daily routine filled with blue and green cards was over.
Leader Tianying, watch my brothers eat this! No, on August 8th, he released a new single,
The brothers who violently landed on the 39th floor brought us a treasure map. Some people may ask, hey,
It’s just a treasure map, what’s so big about it? Shushu has already experienced that treasure.
What if I told you that among the points marked on the treasure map this time, point 8 will be 100% red?
Do you have to rush soon? Hurry up and tell me! Thank you, Brother Leader, Dam Kuangjue treasure map,
Red light flashes and pays directly. This Treasure Month event is really about hunting in the Paifenghuo zone.
The rare and magical dissolving aroma and fragrance gift, Hafk treasure hunting team, will report all the treasure maps to me at the meeting!
The event starts today, and you can choose any of the three legendary bundles with double yellow directly. In hunting time, show your sharp edge,
Or go get some French fries and play tricks? If nothing else works, our Tesla coil will turn the whole place upside down! Ah,
This is really a difficult choice for patients who already have difficulty choosing. Beacon battlefield, explosive rhythm,
Call for double airdrops, get limited gun skins for free, and exclusive gold medals are cool.
No wonder the Hafk Group has been trying to suck the blood of the Asara royal family, and they are shouting slogans that the ground belongs to Asara.
Co-authored because everything buried in the ground is red.
I don’t want outsiders to take it. I can’t bear it anymore. I don’t need to bear it anymore. I can no longer worry about dual-wielding muskets in vain.
It's time to do your part for the sustainability of the royal family of Ashara. Note that
It's not for digging for treasure. You are not allowed to slander me.